Damien Hervieux

Address: 162-0061, Tokyo-to, Shinjuku-ku, Ichigaya-yanagicho, 26, Roje, KR 302

Tel: 080 2982 1443 Nationality: France

Birth: 11/26/85

Visa: Spouse Visa

Webpage: https://www.damienhervieux.com

Email: <u>damien.herv@gmail.com</u>

FullStack Developer

I started my career in June 2018 and worked on various full-stack projects since then. I am currently living in Tokyo with my family. I usually spend my free time with my family, studying code, watching movies or at the jiu-jitsu club.

Experience

FullStack Developer - Rooking Inc. 2018 - present

Barista 2013 ~ 2017 Tokyo (Japan) and Melbourne (Australia)

Project Manager - Publicis Paris (France) 2010 - 2012

Coordinate projects for Renault-Nissan's communication (automobile) at each car launch. Manage the budget, the schedule and the communication between designers, production and client. Each project consisted in a movie production, a photo shoot and papers production (ex: product book, magazine, etc.) and/or updating existing content.

Internships Grenoble (France) 2009 – 2010

Organize amateur and professional events related to the surf, snow, skate area.

Skills

Front-End: Typescript, React, Javascript, Vue, Angular, HTML, CSS, GatsbyJS, NextJS

Back-End: Django, NodeJS, NestJS, Laravel, Python, MySQL, ElasticSearch, Redis,

Fastify

Testing: Jest, Enzyme

Tools: Webpack, Visual Studio Code, JetBrains (PyCharm, ...), EsLint/TSLint, Prettier,

Figma, Trello/Jira, Github/GitLab, SourceTree, Postman

DevOps: AWS S3, AWS Lambda, AWS EC2, AWS ElasticBeanStalk, AWS RDS, CircleCI

Wanted: Rust, Machine Learning, Kotlin, Swift, React Native

Languages

French: Native English: Fluent

Japanese: Basic to Conversational

Education

Master of Economics and Business - Grenoble (France) 2009

Bachelor Degree of Economics - Le Mans (France) 2006

High school degree, major in Science - Le Mans (France) 2002